(Sheldon:)Howard, can I ask you
a question?
(Howard:)No.
(Sheldon:)All right, I'll just
toss this out to the room.
(Sheldon:)Um, I was thinking
that the best way
(Sheldon:)to fight my addiction is by
(Sheldon:)weaning myself off in steps.
(Sheldon:)Now, I couldn't find
a caffeine patch,
(Sheldon:)but I did find
what claims to be
(Sheldon:)a mind-boosting
caffeine suppository.
(Raj:)Yeah.
(Sheldon:)You know, the interesting fact
about the rectum...
Sheldon!
(Leonard:)We are dealing with
an impossible deadline
(Leonard:)from the Air Force
because of you.
(Leonard:)So have an energy drink,
don't have an energy drink.
(Leonard:)Order suppositories
and shove 'em
(Leonard:)wherever you want,
I don't care!
(Sheldon:)You don't shove them.
(Sheldon:)They come with an
easy-glide applicator.
(The Flash:)Right.
Listen to me.
(Leonard:)We can't do anything
until you do your part.
(Leonard:)So get up in front of
this whiteboard and do it!
(Sheldon:)I can't.
Yes, you can.
(Howard:)No...
(Sheldon:)I can't figure out
the math.